Don't fight the feeling.
The Fighting Temptations is a comedy, music,
romance film directed by Jonathan Lynn.
Darrin Hill, a slick-talking but down-on- his-luck NYC advertising exec, returns to
his hometown in Georgia to claim the inheritance his aunt left him.
But before Darrin can collect the money, he must fulfill his
aunt's final wish -- to create a local choir.
Darrin Hill, played by Cuba Gooding Jr..
Lilly, played by Beyoncé.
Lucius, played by Mike Epps.
Maryann Hill, played by Faith Evans.
Miles Smoke, played by Steve Harvey.
Reverend Lewis, played by Wendell Pierce.
The Fighting Temptations is a 2003 American musical comedy film directed by
Jonathan Lynn, written by Elizabeth Hunter and Saladin K.
Patterson, and distributed by Paramount Pictures and MTV Films.
Cuba Gooding Jr.
plays a man who returns to his hometown in Georgia and attempts to revive a church choir in order to enter
a gospel competition, with the help of his childhood friend, played by Beyoncé Knowles.
The film is notable for its soundtrack and ensemble cast.
The film received mixed reviews upon release.
The film explores themes of church choir, romcom, celebratory.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.